Finding Aid for the The Morris Frank Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
The Morris Frank Collection
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0154
2.50 linear_feet
- I. Awards, Citations, Resolutions
  - American Overseas Association Plaque., 1979 (Box 1)
  - Exchange Club of Morristown Book of Golden Deeds., October 4, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Exchange Club of Morristown Honorary Membership for “Buddy” Frank, February 24, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Glmbels' Award Plaque. Educational Week for the Blind., March 4, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Morris County Board of Freeholders Resolution., 1979 (Box 1)
  - Unico National Citation., October 17, 1964 (Box 1)
  - American Legion Citation., 1979 (Box 2)
  - Mendham Township, New Jersey, Juvenile Conference Committee Resolution of Appreciation., September 21, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Morristown, New Jersey, Citation. Mayor Donald Cresitello, May 9, 1978 (Box 2)
  - New Jersey Proclamation: Morris Frank Day Governor Brendan Byrne, September 21, 1979 (Box 2)
  - New Jersey Assembly Resolutions., May 10, 1979 and November 19, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Salvation Army Citation, “Others”., May 6, 1980 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service Special Achievement Award., September 21, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Vanderbilt University Quinq Induction for Morris Frank and Buddy VI., May 26, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Photograph: Buddy II (Box 2)
  - Biographical Cartoon: Morris Frank and Buddy (Box 2)
  - Brooksi.de Church Citation., September 21, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Mendham Township Declaration. Morris Frank Day, September 21, 1979 (Box 3)
  - New Jersey Association of Life Underwriters Resolution. Life Underwriter of the Year, 1980 Morris Frank (with braille plate) (Box 3)
  - Carter, President Jimmie. Congratulatory Telegram., September 21, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Salvation Army of Morristown Certificate of Appreciation., January 27, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Tennessee Colonel Appointment. Governor Henry Horton, July 28, 1931 (Box 4)
- II. Clippings and associated ephemera
  - Seeing Eye Commemorative Stamp - clippings First Day Cover (Box 2)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary--The Seeing Eye, Inc. - clippings 1978 Annual Report (Box 2)
  - Morris Frank Day--Septcmber 21, 1979 - clippings (Box 2)
  - Morris and Lois Frank - clippings (Box 2)
- III. Publications
  - Benz-Briggs, Elenora, “President's Message,” Secretaries Summation (Vol. XXI, No. 3), January, 1981 (Box 2)
  - “Bonnie Tells Her Story,” The Seeing Eye, Inc. (Box 2)
  - “Buddy to Light the Darkness,” The Home Office Shield (Vol. 26, No. 6), June, 1967 (Box 2)
  - “Charitable Canines,” RPh, January, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Frank, Morris, “My Escape from Darkness,” Guideposts, April, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Frank, Morris S. to Byron W. Evans, The Oversea'r (Vol. 31, No.2), June, 1980 (Box 2)
  - “Morris Frank Awarded Book of Golden Deeds,” The New Jersey Exchangite (Vol. XLII, No. 2), November, 1979 (Box 2)
  - “Morris Frank: Pioneer of the Seeing Eye,” Vanderbilt Alumnus (Vol. 64, No. 4), Summer, 1979 (Box 2)
  - “1980 International Humanity Service Award Presented to Morris Frank,” The Oversea'r (Vol. 31, No. 1), April 1980 (Box 2)
  - “The. Seeing Eye,” DOGFANCY (Vol. II, No. 1), February, 1971 (Box 2)
  - “The Seeing Eye,” Beneficial to You (Vol. 13, No. 5), 1980 (Box 2)
  - The Seeing Eye. Brochure (Box 2)
  - “The Working Group,” DOGFANCY (Vol. I, No. 1), October, 1970 (Box 2)